[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "Attraction",
    "back": "atrakcja",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular atrakcja.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna atrakcja.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "front": "Landmark",
    "back": "punkt orientacyjny",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular punkt orientacyjny.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna punkt orientacyjny.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "front": "Monument",
    "back": "pomnik",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular pomnik.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna pomnik.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "front": "Museum",
    "back": "muzeum",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular muzeum.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna muzeum.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "front": "Gallery",
    "back": "galeria (sztuki)",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular galeria (sztuki).",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna galeria (sztuki).",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "front": "Castle",
    "back": "zamek",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular zamek.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna zamek.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "front": "Palace",
    "back": "pałac",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular pałac.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna pałac.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "front": "Park",
    "back": "park",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular park.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna park.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "front": "Beach",
    "back": "plaża",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular plaża.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna plaża.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "front": "Forest",
    "back": "las, puszcza",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular las, puszcza.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna las, puszcza.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "front": "Mountain",
    "back": "góra",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular góra.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna góra.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "front": "National park",
    "back": "park narodowy",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular park narodowy.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna park narodowy.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "front": "Botanical garden",
    "back": "ogród botaniczny",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular ogród botaniczny.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna ogród botaniczny.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "front": "Aquarium",
    "back": "akwarium",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular akwarium.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna akwarium.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "front": "Zoo",
    "back": "zoo, ogród zoologiczny",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular zoo, ogród zoologiczny.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna zoo, ogród zoologiczny.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "front": "Historical site",
    "back": "miejsce historyczne",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular miejsce historyczne.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna miejsce historyczne.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "front": "Temple",
    "back": "świątynia",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular świątynia.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna świątynia.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "front": "Cathedral",
    "back": "katedra",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular katedra.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna katedra.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "front": "Church",
    "back": "kościół",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular kościół.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna kościół.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "front": "Ruins",
    "back": "ruiny",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular ruiny.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna ruiny.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "front": "Square",
    "back": "plac",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular plac.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna plac.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "front": "Town hall",
    "back": "ratusz",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular ratusz.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna ratusz.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "front": "Stadium",
    "back": "stadion",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular stadion.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna stadion.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "front": "Harbour/port",
    "back": "port",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular port.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna port.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "front": "Amusement park",
    "back": "park rozrywki",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular park rozrywki.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna park rozrywki.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "front": "Cave",
    "back": "jaskinia",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular jaskinia.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna jaskinia.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "front": "Ruin",
    "back": "ruina",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular ruina.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna ruina.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "front": "Island",
    "back": "wyspa",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular wyspa.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna wyspa.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "front": "River",
    "back": "rzeka",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular rzeka.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna rzeka.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "front": "Lake",
    "back": "jezioro",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular jezioro.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna jezioro.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "front": "Viewpoint",
    "back": "punkt widokowy, obserwacyjny",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular punkt widokowy, obserwacyjny.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna punkt widokowy, obserwacyjny.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "front": "Sculpture",
    "back": "rzeźba",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular rzeźba.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna rzeźba.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "front": "Bridge",
    "back": "most",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular most.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna most.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "front": "Marketplace",
    "back": "rynek, targ",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular rynek, targ.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna rynek, targ.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "front": "Shopping mall",
    "back": "centrum handlowe",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular centrum handlowe.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna centrum handlowe.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "front": "Street market",
    "back": "targ uliczny",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular targ uliczny.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna targ uliczny.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "front": "Skyscraper",
    "back": "wieżowiec",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular wieżowiec.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna wieżowiec.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "front": "Village",
    "back": "wioska",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular wioska.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna wioska.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "front": "Resort",
    "back": "kurort",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular kurort.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna kurort.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "front": "Tourist information centre",
    "back": "centrum informacji turystycznej",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular centrum informacji turystycznej.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna centrum informacji turystycznej.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "front": "Hot spring",
    "back": "gorące źródło",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "This is a popular gorące źródło.",
    "backExample": "To jest popularna gorące źródło.",
    "remembered": false
  }
]